[
    {
        "question": "What are the seven data protection principles?",
        "answer": ["Lawfulness", "Purpose", "Data-Minimisation", "Storage", "Security", "Accuracy", "Accountability"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Area covered by a single legal system and a set of laws",
      "answer": ["jurisdiction"]
    },
    {
      "question": "England, Scotland, Wales, Northern Ireland (excluding Channel Islands, Isle of Man)",
      "answer": ["United Kingdom"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Organisation that has been incorporated to give it the same legal status as a natural person",
      "answer": ["legal person"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Court action under the criminal law",
      "answer": ["criminal litigation"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Organisation that prosecutes a person for a criminal offence",
      "answer": ["crown prosecution service"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Person being prosecuted in a criminal case",
      "answer": ["defendant"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Test used to prosecute a person on criminal law",
      "answer": ["beyond reasonable doubt"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A body of people chosen to listen to all facts in a court trial and decide guilt or innocence",
      "answer": ["jury"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Individual who oversees a court case and decides the penalties",
      "answer": ["judge"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a reason for appeal in criminal law?",
      "options": [
        "Quash conviction",
        "Order new trial",
        "Increase penalty",
        "Dismiss case"
      ],
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "Court action under the civil law",
      "answer": ["civil litigation"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Party that initiates a civil litigation",
      "answer": ["claimant"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Test used to prosecute a person on civil law",
      "answer": ["balance of probabilities"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following can result in a civil law case?",
      "options": [
        "Contracts",
        "Libel",
        "Family Law",
        "Criminal activity"
      ],
      "answer": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which court in the hierarchy deals specifically with criminal cases?",
      "options": [
        "Magistrates",
        "County Court",
        "Crown Court",
        "European Court of Justice"
      ],
      "answer": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which court typically handles civil cases without a jury?",
      "options": [
        "County Court",
        "Supreme Court",
        "Crown Court",
        "Magistrates' Court"
      ],
      "answer": 0
    }
]